# Novita Dian Anugraheni

## Data Science Intern

Address: Karanganyar, Jawa Tengah, Indonesia
Phone: +6287728570987
WhatsApp: +6287773718611

• Email: anugraheninovita04@gmail.com • LinkedIn: Novita Dian Anugraheni • Portofolio: novitadian20

I am 6th semester student of Informatics Department. I am teamwork oriented, and responsible Data Scientist with significant experience in creating reports and presentations. I'm also an Innovative and scientifically rigorous student with significant data science Internship experience to bring to the company. Sufficiently educated and professional certification as Junior Data Scientist by RMDS, also professional certification in Visualization Data, Processing Data for Analysis Data, Mathematic Analytics, and Prediction Modelling (ML). Trilingual in Bahasa, English, Mandarin.

## **EDUCATION**

#### Bangkit Student by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka (2022)

- Machine Learning Path
- Feb 2022 Jun 2022

## Nanjing Xiaozhuang University, China

- Informatics
- Aug 2021 Aug 2023

#### Atma Jaya Yogyakarta University, Indonesia

- Informatics
- Aug 2019 Aug 2023

- Learn the key concepts and applications of AI to solve a wide range of Machine Learning problems and Deep Learning.
- GPA: 3.882 / 4.00
- Joint Degree Program (2+2)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Big Data Analytics PT Kimia Farma, [Virtual Internship]

May 2022 - Jun 2022

Data and Machine Learning Specialist

**KitaBisa.com** [Project Company]

Jakarta

Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

Data Scientist

PT Prima Print [Internship]

Surabaya

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

Job Description :

- Building cloud platforms for the development of company applications.
- Managing the communications between the internal system and the survey vendor.
- Maintaining production systems.

#### Job Description:

- Building House Classification model for Management Scholarships using CNN.
- Build OCR model for validating ID Card and files.
- Processing data using python for the scoring applicants.

## Job Description :

- Conduct exploratory data analysis and grab insights from the data
- Build predictive models and machine-learning algorithms
- Present information using data visualization techniques
- Participate actively in scientific paper discussions
- Writing reports and documentation based on discussions and experimentations

## Lecturer Assistant (statistics), Atma Jaya Yogyakarta University

Yogyakarta

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

Lecturer Assistant (mathematic discrete)

Yogyakarta

Jan 2021 - Aug 2021

## Job Description :

- Teaching about related material for 3rd semester students
- Make exam questions
- Analyze grades or score for the students
- Provide material enrichment

## **SKILLS & LANGUAGES**

- Exploratory data analysis and grab insights from the data
- Writing reports and documentations based on data
- Strong verbal and written communication skills
- Processing data using data science-related libraries and tools (NumPy, pandas, scikit learn, google spreadsheet)
- Data Visualisation (matplotlib, tableau)
- Mathematics (Statistics analysis and Computer Science)
- Machine Learning (Model Development)
- Deep Learning (NLP, OCR, TensorFlow framework, Information Retrieval by scraping)
- programming paradigm (structured / object oriented programming python Implementation, SQL)

## Communication Languages:

o Bahasa Indonesia (Native), English (Professional Working Proficiency), Mandarin (Intermediate)

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

• Selected Team for Company Project Bangkit by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka (2022) 1'st Place

• Best Students Informatics Class of 2021 Nanjing Xiaozhuang University (2021) 3'rd Place

Awardee FGA Digital Talent Scholarship by KOMNIFO
 (2021)

Awardee Nanjing Municipal China Government Scholarship 2021-2023 (2021)

Delegation National English Debate in ALSA (UGM)
 (2019) Semifinal Stage

• State Bahasa Debate Competition (2017) 1'st Place

## **ORGANISATION & VOLUNTEER**

PPIT Nanjing (Perhimpunan Pelajar-Pelajar Indonesia-Nanjing, Tiongkok, China)

The state of the state of

The student organization for Indonesian students who are studying in China.

• CTC (Critical Thinking Community)

English Debate Club that prepared to take part in the competition.

• I2C (National Informatics competition part of IFEST#8)

Organized more than 50 members in this organisation.

I prepared for about 6 months and organized more than 80 committee members for this event.

• Himaforka (Himpunan Mahasiswa Informatika)

Computer engineering student organizations from various generations.

• International Bebras Community in Yogyakarta

Train logic algorithm that related to coding for teenagers for about more than 40 students

ARJUNA (Journalistic Community)

Medcominfo 2021-2022

Public Relation

2019- 2021

President

2019 - 2020

**Medcominfo** 2019 - 2021

**Trainer** 2019

President

2017-2018